export const quiz9 = {
    topic: 'OCD',
    totalQuestions: 10,
    questions: [
        {
            question : "How often you ever experience unwanted repetitive and persistent thoughts that cause you anxiety?",
            answers : ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question : "Do you fear contamination (i.e. germs) from people or the environment and engage in excessive cleaning? If so, how often?",
            answers : ["Yes","No"]
          },
          {
            question : "Do you follow excessive hand washing, showering and tooth brushing",
            answers : ["Yes","No"]
          },
          {
            question : "Do you engage in rituals that provide temporary relief to your anxiety, such as counting or checking ?",
            answers : ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question : "Have you ever tried to hide these thoughts or behaviors from others?",
            answers : ["Yes","No"]
          },
          {
            question : "How often you mentally repeat words or numbers a certain number of times, or concentrate on good or safe numbers",
            answers : ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question : "Do you belive in touching, tapping or moving in a particular way or a certain number of times",
            answers : ["Yes","No"]
          },
          {
            question : "Needing to constantly ask questions or confess to seek reassurance",
            answers : ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question : "How often you feel distressed or upset by these thoughts and behaviors?",
            answers : ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question : "Do you recognize that these thoughts and behaviors might not make logical sense, but you still can't stop them?",
            answers : ["Yes","No"]
          }
    ],
  }